He killed a lot of robots
他杀了很多机器人
Do you believe him?
你相信他吗？
The last person you should trust is yourself, right?
你最不应该信任的人就是你自己，对吗？
Do you remember that day in the car?
你还记得那天在车里吗？
I saw you kill Anyang with my own eyes
我亲眼看见你杀了安阳
It's you
是你
You are still in front of An Qiu
你还在安秋面前
pretend to be a good person
假装自己是个好人
Apparently you were the first one to push me.
显然你是第一个推我的人
You are the one with the knife in your hand
你是手里拿着刀的人
You are also the one who captured the robot.
你也是俘虏了机器人的人。
You are the one who dare not admit to killing someone
你是那个不敢承认杀人的人
do you know
你知道吗
chew
嚼
sorry
对不起
I admit
我承认
i seize the chance
我抓住机会
I gave you many opportunities
我给过你很多机会
Available from start to finish
从头到尾都可用
they are all lying to me
他们都在骗我
You must think I'm stupid, right?
你一定觉得我很傻吧？
I killed my brother's murderer
我杀了杀害我兄弟的凶手
as a companion
作为同伴
as a friend
作为朋友
sorry
对不起
Shen Li
沉李
how
如何
I've considered three sets and want to go back.
我已经考虑了三套并想回去。
how so
怎么会这样
After getting a new set, I get off work on time every day.
换了新一套后，我每天都准时下班。
It's too late to be happy
幸福的时候已经晚了
do your thing
做你的事
OK
好的
What exactly will you do?
你到底会做什么？
I just want to seek justice for An Qiu
我只想为安秋讨回公道
Qingnu lied to you
青女骗了你
Just like Luo Su lied to me back then
就像罗苏当年骗我一样
Your brother died mysteriously
你的兄弟神秘死亡
Someone must want to help him take revenge
一定有人想帮他报仇
An Qiu, don’t believe him
安秋你别信他
if you take action
如果你采取行动
I will be like him
我会成为像他一样的人
From today on she will be your new partner
从今天起她将成为你的新搭档
Are you worried about me?
你担心我吗？
you are different from them
你和他们不一样
It’s different from place to place, and it’s different from place to place.
各地都不一样，各地也不一样。
you are important to me
你对我很重要
An Qiu, don’t believe him
安秋你别信他
Anyang's death won't make you take action
安阳的死也无法让你采取行动
it seems
它似乎
Even your initial obsession has been changed by them
连你最初的执念都被他们改变了
Beyond the initial obsession
除了最初的痴迷
What other reason do you have to protect him like this?
你还有什么理由要这样保护他？
This is what you think about Android
这是你对安卓的看法
experimental evidence
实验证据
I let this happen
我让这一切发生
Mingmou would never do this
明谋绝对不会这么做
Yin Tianhong
尹天红
I found that many robots are looking at Mingming
我发现很多机器人都在看着明明
I heard that even your mother participated in Mingmu's experiment.
听说明木的实验连你妈妈都参与了。
What qualifications do you have to accuse me?
你有什么资格指责我？
Yin Tianhong
尹天红
Have you ever wondered why you are in bright eyes?
你有没有想过，为什么你会在明亮的眼睛里？
You obviously hate Qingnuo
你明明很讨厌青诺
Why do we still believe and support him?
为什么我们仍然相信并支持他？
Don't you dare do anything to him
你不敢对他做什么
Your brother told me
你哥哥告诉我的
Your main concern is taking care of your family
您最关心的是照顾家人
But you have become a bright-eyed experience
但你却成了明眸的经历
He also wanted to protect the man who killed his brother
他也想保护杀害他兄弟的人
Don't they need to be punished?
他们不需要受到惩罚吗？
Let the tragedy end
让悲剧结束吧
chew
嚼
Cheng Nu
程女
Qingnu, where are you?
青女，你在哪里？
Why are you here?
你为什么在这？
Who was kidnapped?
谁被绑架了？
Is he related to Anqiu?
他和安丘有关系吗？
Nothing to do with this
与此无关
This is what Yin Tianhong did
这是殷天鸿干的
He also kidnapped An Qiu
他还绑架了安秋
What
什么
Then I have to call the headquarters quickly.
那我得赶紧给总部打电话了
Don't say it yet
还别说
We still don’t know what Yin Tianhong will do
我们还不知道殷天鸿会做什么
I am anxious
我很担心
Chiyo will be in danger
千代将会有危险
You have begun to care about your partner
你已经开始关心你的伴侣了
thank you for coming
感谢你的到来
We are also partners, why should you be grateful?
我们也是合作伙伴，你为什么要感恩？
it seems
它似乎
Even your initial obsession has been changed by them
连你最初的执念都被他们改变了
correct
正确的
Do you know the experiment my mother did?
你知道我妈妈做过的实验吗？
Dr. Zhang’s experiments have been kept secret
张博士的实验一直保密
But I know she is cooperating with Ming
但我知道她是在和明某合作
Laboratory funding and resources
实验室资金及资源
They are all taken from inside the bright eye.
它们都是从亮眼内部取出的。
Enter
进入
you came just in time
你来得正是时候
I just have something to ask you
我正好有事想问你
Chu Chen made a request
楚辰提出了一个要求
I need to check on the monitoring of your three groups.
我需要检查一下你们三个小组的监控情况。
He suspects you plan to destroy evidence
他怀疑你打算销毁证据
how so
怎么会这样
He has hated me for a long time.
他恨我很久了。
It must be about Xu Nianyan
一定是徐一年的事
make him feel embarrassed
让他感到尴尬
Why are you so nervous?
你为什么这么紧张？
Why am I nervous?
我怎么会紧张呢？
just me
只有我
I really can't stand it
我实在受不了
how old are you?
你今年多大？
Still noisy like a baby
还是像个婴儿一样吵闹
Chu Chen is like this now
楚辰现在就是这个样子
I'll take care of it
我会处理的
are you looking for me?
你在找我吗？
Do you know what my mom went through?
你知道我妈妈的经历吗？
Why do you remember to ask this?
你为什么记得问这个？
her experience
她的经历
Will it replace the original obsession?
它会取代最初的痴迷吗？
How do you know this?
你怎么会知道这事？
so it's true
所以这是真的
correct
正确的
Bright Eyes in the Android calling sequence
Bright Eyes 在 Android 调用顺序中
Created after release
发行后创建
The dose wasn't even identified at first.
一开始甚至没有识别剂量。
Judgment robot
判断机器人
takes a long time
需要很长时间
Thank you mom for staying with me
谢谢你妈妈陪我一起
I developed an identification potion
我开发了一种识别药水
Significantly improve detection efficiency
显着提高检测效率
However, identification potions cannot be used casually.
不过鉴定药剂可不能随便使用
After several miscalculations by androids,
在发生了几次仿生人的误算事件之后，
Bright eyes in crisis
明亮的眼睛陷入危机
your mother suggested
你妈妈建议
Robot focuses on his original obsession
机器人专注于他最初的痴迷
if this was their original obsession
如果这是他们最初的痴迷
Be a useful person to society
做一个对社会有用的人
Maybe we can break this situation
也许我们可以打破这种局面
So try this thing
所以试试这个东西
This is decided by the two of you.
这是你们俩决定的。
Yes
是的
But I discovered your mother's experience
但我发现了你母亲的经历
It brings a lot of pain to Android
它给Android带来了很大的痛苦
I also advised her
我还劝她
On the grounds that Ming no longer supports her
以明某不再支持她为由
tell her to stop
告诉她停下来
but
但
She insisted on continuing
她坚持要继续
she also told me
她也告诉我
Even if Mingmou doesn't participate
即使明眸不参加
You'll also find others to collaborate with
您还会发现其他人可以合作
She was angry because I didn't support her.
她很生气，因为我不支持她。
Then he didn't even answer my calls.
后来他甚至不接我的电话。
Why do you persist?
你为什么坚持？
Change initial obsession
改变最初的执念
perhaps
或许
because of you
因为有你
When you enter bright eyes
当你进入明亮的双眼后
Is your relationship getting worse?
你们的关系是不是越来越差了？
So I can understand her approach
所以我能理解她的做法
as a mother
作为母亲
She hopes to cultivate a
她希望培养一名
it can protect you
它可以保护你
Completely loyal to your Android partner
完全忠诚于您的 Android 合作伙伴
replace it
代替它
stay with you
留在你身边
presumptuous
放肆
problem appear
出现问题
you killed the robot
你杀了机器人
But I didn't know he was your brother at the time
但当时我并不知道他是你的兄弟
Who abuses robots?
谁滥用机器人？
we never do that
我们从不这样做
I didn't expect An Qiu to be a robot.
没想到安秋是个机器人。
What's even more ridiculous is that she is already at dawn.
更可笑的是，她已经在明暮了。
Now we will be in pain
现在我们会很痛苦
Those photos you just saw
那些你刚刚看到的照片
Just bright eyes
只是眼睛明亮
Control the life and death of all androids
控制所有仿生人的生死权
abuse of power
滥用职权妄为
What happened to the video in Yin Tianhong’s hand?
殷天鸿手里的视频怎么了？
Obviously, the place of abuse was not in Ming.
显然，施虐地点并不在明某
This is slander
这是诽谤
beside
旁边
What’s wrong with you
你怎么了
I saw him this morning
我今天早上看见他了
I didn't know he could take videos
我不知道他会拍视频
minister
部长
There is a group of reporters outside
外面有一群记者
He refuses to leave no matter what
他无论如何都不肯离开
I'll handle the live broadcast issues
直播问题我来处理
You must first find a way to help me find An Qiu
你首先得想办法帮我找到安秋
Tomorrow evening
明天晚上
I will reveal all the truth
我将揭露所有真相
Is it right to obviously abuse your power?
明默滥用职权是否正确？
correct
正确的
Is it right to hide the truth?
隐瞒真相是否正确？
It's the same as murder, isn't it?
这和谋杀是一样的，不是吗？
correct
正确的
Minister Wan is here. Minister Wan is here.
万部长来了 万部长来了
Minister Wan, Minister Wan
万部长，万部长
what do you think?
你觉得怎么样？
A case-handling officer abused his power
明某办案人员滥用职权
Things that hurt robots
伤害机器人的事情
1. The so-called assault incident
一、所谓袭人事件
This did not happen in Mingmu
这在明穆并没有发​​生
We will contact Mingmo headquarters
我们会联系明墨总部
Investigation into this incident
对此事件的调查
Minister Wan
万部长
mentioned in the video
视频中提到的
Robots with sparkling eyes watching you search
眼睛闪闪发光地看着你搜索的机器人
conduct harsh experiments
进行严酷的实验
Can you prove this?
你能证明这一点吗？
Dianyan tortures the robot from top to bottom
亮眼从上到下虐待机器人
i repeat
我重复
Bright eyes will never allow abuse to exist
明亮的眼睛绝不允许虐待的存在
The sister of the robot who was killed in the movie
电影中被杀的机器人的妹妹
He's the bright-eyed detective
他是那个眼睛明亮的侦探
What is Ming's major?
请问明某的专业是什么？
This is actually an internal mistake on our part.
这实际上是我们内部的错误。
Minister Wan’s thoughts during this live broadcast
万部长在这次直播中的感想
What do you want to respond to?
你想回应什么？
I remind everyone
我提醒大家
Who planned this live broadcast?
谁策划了这场直播
He is an android serial killer.
他是一个安卓连环杀手。
police arrested him
警方逮捕了他
I also hope that the general public
也希望广大民众
Do we really want to do this?
我们真的想这样做吗？
Just do this
只要这样做
Only in this way can everyone
只有这样大家才能
Get to know Mingmo’s true face
认识明默的真面目
dismantle them completely
将它们彻底拆除
Will he come?
他会来吗？
He will definitely come
他一定会来
Wanbo asked me to come over and help temporarily.
万博让我暂时过来帮忙。
It’s not you who enters samadhi
不是你进入三摩地
Don't you think it's strange?
你不觉得很奇怪吗？
Yin Tianhong’s goal has always been to kill the androids
殷天鸿的目标一直是杀死仿生人
But not only did he not kill Anqiu,
但他不但没有杀安丘，
and set a trap for her
并给她设下陷阱
What is his goal?
他的目标是什么？
Kill more androids?
杀死更多的仿生人？
And then there's his initial obsession
然后是他最初的痴迷
Is he just killing robots?
难道他只是在杀死机器人吗？
Why do employers buy cyborgs?
为什么雇主会购买电子人？
This led to his initial obsession with killing robots
这让他最初对杀死机器人产生了痴迷
Why is it impossible?
为什么不可能呢？
Some owners are afraid to do it themselves
有的业主不敢自己动手
So buy a robot
所以买个机器人
Just to experience the fun of killing
只为体验杀戮的乐趣
Even though his original obsession was killing robots
即使他最初的痴迷是杀死机器人
Also requires a switch to start
还需要一个开关才能启动
Qingnu lied to you
青女骗了你
Just like Luo Su lied to me back then
就像罗苏当年骗我一样
Your brother died mysteriously
你的兄弟神秘死亡
Someone must want to help him take revenge
一定有人想帮他报仇
If this is the case
如果是这样
Sister Gu
顾姐
The last survey you conducted contains results.
您上次进行的调查包含结果。
This is Lao Qin
这就是老秦
It turns out that he is a security guard at Dreamland Club.
原来，他是梦境俱乐部的保安。
A few months ago I suddenly started looking for a buyer.
几个月前我突然开始寻找买家。
Want to sell your Dream Club?
想出售梦境俱乐部吗？
same period
同期
Large sums of money began to be transferred into his account
大笔的钱开始汇入他的账户
I also found the suspicious account from which the payment was made.
我还找到了付款的可疑帐户。
Why you?
为什么你？
In broad daylight you panic
光天化日之下你陷入了恐慌
Are you afraid of anything?
你害怕什么吗？
If someone attacks you from behind
如果有人在背后偷袭你
Are not you afraid?
你不害怕吗？
Are you afraid of Lao Chen?
你怕的是老陈吗？
What are you afraid of?
你怕什么呢？
At most it's just a small ditch
最多就是一条小沟而已
walk around
四处走走
That's it
就是这样
Then who are you afraid of?
那你还怕谁呢？
It's Losu
是洛苏
Still Yin Tianhong
还是殷天红
You are the owner of Dream Club
您是梦境俱乐部的老板
I do not know what you're talking about
我不知道你在说什么
six years ago
六年前
you are in dream club
你在梦境俱乐部
Illegal operation of electronic entertainment projects
非法经营电子娱乐项目
After announcing the summons
宣布传唤后
Instead, they went underground
相反，他们转入地下
Also looking for new robots
也在寻找新的机器人
I was seriously violated
我被严重侵犯了
Saiyuan City’s “Robot Prohibition Law”
西原市《禁止机器人法》
Who did you hear this from?
你是从谁那里听到这句话的？
Is it Lao Chen?
是老陈吗？
This guy of his is a thief
他的这个人是个小偷
You believe everything he says
你相信他说的一切
i don't trust anyone
我不相信任何人
I only believe in evidence
我只相信证据
We found the surveillance system in the basement of Lao Chen's house
我们在老陈家的地下室发现了监控系统
It contains the records of many of your meetings.
里面有你多次会议的记录
Do you want to borrow Lao Chen's hand?
你想借老陈的手吗？
Club was sold secretly
俱乐部被秘密出售
The account used to transfer money to Lao Qin is also in your name.
给老秦转账的账户也在你名下。
The witnesses and physical evidence are all there
人证、物证都在
If you still don't tell the truth
如果你还是不说实话
Let us discuss these issues elsewhere.
这些问题我们到别处再谈吧。
I just want to know the truth about Luosu's death
我只是想知道罗苏死亡的真相
Rossu was one of the club's first players
罗苏是俱乐部首批球员之一
android receptionist
安卓接待员
Later I got sick
后来我生病了
He is no longer fit to be a receptionist
他不再适合当接待员
Staying in the club will only scare away customers
留在俱乐部只会吓跑顾客
I couldn't help but kick her out hard
我忍不住狠狠地把她踢出去
But Luo Su was unwilling to do this
但罗苏却不愿意这么做
She begged me many times to let her back.
她多次恳求我让她回来。
Boss, please let me come back
老板，请让我回来吧
you look like this now
你现在看起来像这样
I'm no longer cut out to be a receptionist.
我不再适合当接待员了。
As long as I don't leave the club
只要我不离开俱乐部
i can do anything
我什么事都能做
You can do anything you want, can your mind do it?
你可以做任何你想做的事，你的头脑能做到吗？
clear
清楚
look at yourself
看看你自己
look at what it looks like now
看看现在的样子
Even if you flush the toilet
就算冲厕所
People are going to hate you, okay?
人们会恨你，好吗？
president
总统
I have other things to do
我还有别的事要做
I can help the club with other things
我可以在其他事情上帮助俱乐部
I can help the club recruit robots
我可以帮助俱乐部招募机器人
Work as a receptionist
担任接待员
at all costs
不惜一切代价
The club was seriously short of players at the time.
当时俱乐部严重缺人
Seeing how pitiful she was, I agreed.
我看她这么可怜，就答应了。
She was the one who recruited Yin Tianhong.
她是招揽殷天鸿的人。
The night Luo Su was murdered
罗苏被害当晚
Why is she back at the club?
她为什么又回到俱乐部？
That day is her birthday
那天是她的生日
She also invited many people to the club
她还邀请了很多人来俱乐部
But who would have thought
但谁能想到
Birthday turned into death anniversary
生日变成了忌日
Yin Tianhong is here too
殷天鸿也来了
Why did Yin Tianhong say that?
尹天鸿为何这么说
Russell betrayed him
罗素背叛了他
I have already sent a message to Cheng Nuo
我已经给程诺发消息了
about there
差不多了
I have a question
我有个问题
What was your first obsession?
你最初的痴迷是什么？
I do not remember
我不记得了
Maybe they were experimenting on me
也许是他们在我身上做的实验
Caused?
造成的？
Of course it's not important
当然这不重要
Anyway, I'm just a nobody
无论如何，我只是一个小人物
those who don't care about them
那些不关心他们的人
But until I met Luo Su
但直到遇见罗苏
I understand your pain
我理解你的痛苦
why not?
为什么不？
look at me
看着我
love this experience
喜欢这种经历
after tonight
今晚之后
there will be an end
将会有一个结束
after everything is over
一切结束后
let's get out of here
我们离开这里吧
What's wrong
怎么了
What has been lost?
失去了什么？
roll
卷
Now that it's solved
既然已经解决了
can you tell me then
那你能告诉我吗
What is your purpose in doing all this?
你做这一切的目的是什么？
What are you so worried about?
你这么担心什么？
just started
刚刚开始
I think everyone is familiar with the face behind me
我想大家都熟悉我身后的脸
It should be very familiar.
应该很熟悉吧。
That's right, it was the one before
没错，就是之前的
Admit that you are taking advantage of your position
承认你正在利用你的职位
The bright-eyed detective who persecutes androids at will
随意迫害仿生人的明眸侦探
Cheng Nu
程女
Apparently you killed more androids
显然你杀了更多的仿生人
Who are you to judge me?
你是谁来评判我？
I admit
我承认
Do you admit it?
你承认吗？
Or is it someone else's fault again?
还是又是别人的错？
That was not what I meant
我不是这个意思
Why people?
为什么是人？
always blame others
总是责备别人
To cover up one's mistakes
为了掩盖自己的错误
messenger of justice
正义的使者
Don’t you all need to think about it for yourself?
难道大家不需要自己思考一下吗？
take a look at this
看一下这个
This is the question Qingnv asked
这是青女问的问题
The live broadcast should be here
直播应该在这里
He notified the police and left immediately
他通知了警方并立即离开
After a few years, I realized something
几年后，我意识到一件事
Instead of killing with a knife
而不是用刀杀人
verbal violence
言语暴力
and emotional abuse
以及精神虐待
He is the one who really pushes people into the abyss.
真正把人推入深渊的，是他。
You should know that your mother suffered from depression before she was alive, right?
你应该知道你母亲生前就患有抑郁症吧？
I hear you, son, don't know anything about it
我听说你，儿子，对此一无所知
you before death
死之前的你
he fought a good fight
他打了一场精彩的仗
Cut off the relationship between mother and child
断绝母子关系
He told her to find a robot for a son
他告诉她找一个机器人作为儿子
So according to your logic
所以按照你的逻辑
Your mother fell to death that night
那天晚上你母亲摔死了
It's everyone's fault
都是大家的错
With you is a son who doesn't care about his mother.
和你在一起的是不关心母亲的儿子
Not important at all, right?
根本不重要，对吧？
damn it
该死的
I also have a responsibility
我也有责任
Advanced
高级的
I admit
我承认
but
但
Now that I admit it
既然我承认了
Are there any penalties?
有处罚吗？
I'm here today
今天我来了
Just to atone
只为赎罪
I am willing to atone for Anyang's death
我愿意为安阳的死赎罪
To atone for your sins and make you a guinea pig
为你赎罪，让你成为小白鼠
chew
嚼
you can kill me
你可以杀了我
if you do
如果你这样做
Let you make your own words
让你做你自己的话语
chew
嚼
You don't just avenge your brother
你不只是为你的兄弟报仇
At the same time, all robots should also be informed
同时，所有的机器人也应该被告知
We can also break through our initial obsessions
我们也能突破最初的执念
You can also live for yourself
你也可以为自己而活